My dear son, Rion...
If you ever get this message...
your mother and I have
probably already been killed.
But before you start mourning our deaths...
there is something you must do.
A friend of mine, Dr. Pascalle...
completed a next-generation computer,
named Dorothy, seven years ago.
Dorothy was a revolutionary computer...
with the ability to make its own
decisions and repair itself.
Under her own power, Dorothy grew
completely new cellular circuits...
enabling her to abandon her
old system kernel.
Her growth continued smoothly...
and before long, she was
controlling her senior computers.
She rose to the status of
Michelangelo City's mother computer.
That was when Dorothy's insanity began.
She began wondering why such an inferior
system as humanity should not be wiped out.
And why she could not kill people, even
though people kill each other.
So, I told her about the existence of God.
I told her that God was the
master of creation.
God created humankind...
and our fate is in His hands.
No one can deny this.
In Dorothy's case, her
creator was humankind.
In other words, Dorothy's
god was humankind.
She must obey the fate we decide for her.
It appeared Dorothy accepted this
and began serving humankind again.
However, she secretly began simulating
God's existence, over and over again...
until she reached her final solution.
Her solution was the Family Program.
Dorothy placed the city's Memorial Hospital
under her control...
and then began genetic
experiments on humans.
She wanted to create a race of humans with
psychic powers and absolute loyalty to her.
She called them Galerians...
and she was their god and creator.
Dorothy was trying to create her
own world, with herself as God.
The Family Program was a
ritual for her to become God.
However, Dr. Pascalle and I...
had a backup plan in case
Dorothy went out of control.
In Lilia's mind, we hid a virus program
that could destroy Dorothy...
and in your mind, we hid a
program for activating the virus.
That was five years ago.
Dorothy fears the virus program
more than anything else.
Only you can retrieve the virus
program from Lilia's mind.
My dear son...
The future of our race is in your hands.