Rion...
They're coming...
They're looking for me.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
I'm coming.
I'll get there before they do.
Who's that? Rion?!
Yes, it's me, Lilia.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember you very well.
Rion... what did they do to you?
I don't know, but don't worry.
I'll protect you.
I must protect you.
- Why are you crying?
- It's just as Papa said.
He said you would come for me.
He told me to keep sending telepathic
messages to my doll until I contact you.
Lilia, where are you?
Where are you calling from?
In Michelangelo City.
The Babylon Hotel.
I'll be there soon, Lilia.
Hurry, Rion!
That hurt!
You better tell me where Lilia is!
Your memory's coming back, isn't it?
So, you've been watching me?
Ever since you escaped from the hospital.
I think I'm gonna short-circuit!
I've never enjoyed anything this much!