Lilia!
Rion...
My father's dead, isn't he?
I called for him, but there's no reply.
You look so tired...
Have they hurt you?
I've been secretly moving from
place to place over the past month.
But don't worry; I'm OK.
I've heard your voice in my
mind so many times...
Telepathy lets two minds become one.
I can feel your suffering.
When you feel pain, I feel it, too.
I'm sorry I took so long.
- Your voice helped me so much.
- Congratulations!
You found her.
- Who are you?
- Rita.
I've come to bash her brains in.
Are you a Galerian, too?
Mother fears the virus program
hidden in Lilia's mind.
Mother can't even sleep at night.
You humans are such fools.
Our fate lies solely in Mother's hands.
Now I shall avenge my dear brother.
See, Rainheart wasn't too bright,
but he was my pride and joy.
He was gentle as could be, don't you see?
He was the only brother that I had left.
That is why I'm going to make sure that
you die a slow and extremely painful death.
Lilia!
Don't worry! I know that I can disrupt
her psychokinesis with my power!
You little punk!
Lilia!