You're a worthy opponent, Rion.
How about this? With this...
- ... I'll be able to crush you.
- No!
- You're too weak!
- Mother told me that moment of shorting...
- feels oh-so-good.
- Don't.
- You've gone insane.
- We're all slowly but surely going mad.
You just haven't realized it yet.
- Almost...
- Rion!
- Just a little longer...
- Stay away!
Don't kill Rion!
Are you alright?
Don't worry about me.
I don't like myself anyway.
Oh, I hate this power that I possess!
I always wanted the end to come...
but... I never would die.
What a beautiful snow...
It's like having a terrifying
and wonderful vision.
If Mother is God, why would she
inflict you with such a cruel fate?
Where did your true self go?
You are now nothing but an empty
vessel pretending to be human.
We'll never meet again...
It's too bad.
Rion...
I beg you, please destroy me!
My head aches so!
- Please, it hurts so bad!
- Don't!
- Lilia... it's the only way.
- I just can't stand it anymore!
She's decided she wants to die now.
But...
Please...
just do it!
I can't stand it any longer, either.
Please forgive me.
No!
Lilia, please don't cry.
Rion...
you...
where did you get such power?
I was experimented on in the hospital.
They used various PPECs on me.
Don't believe it...
What is it?
It's nothing.
Birdman died laughing.
Rainheart died frightened.
And...
Rita died hating herself.
Those kids injected with PPECs now live
in fear of Dorothy, the mother computer.
But she lives in fear of a virus program
They all live where the
networks converge...
in the Mushroom Tower, high
above Michelangelo City.
I must destroy Dorothy.
Nothing can stop me now...
not even the dark city night
that fills my heart with fear.