This is the only one with no name.
That's you, Rion.
- Who are you?!
- Cain.
Quite a resemblance,
don't you think?
I mean, we're brothers, after all.
What the hell is going on?
You're not as bright as I thought.
You're my kid brother.
The real Rion died at
Michelangelo Hospital.
You're lying!
You know what?
You and I were born here together.
Rion's memory, including the
virus activation program...
was implanted in your mind, and your
appearance was altered to look like him.
Then you were sent out to find Lilia.
Did you really think you escaped
from the hospital all by yourself?
No, I am Rion!
If so, then why do you have
the same powers as us?
You never thought about that, did you?
Who was your mother?
Who was your father?
You'll probably say you have
lots of childhood memories.
But do you really think they're real?
You are a Galerian.
You're one of Dorothy's children.
He's lying, Rion!
They're just trying to
trick you all over again!
The truth is, I really
wanted to go get Lilia...
but Mother chose you instead.
That really hurt.
Still, Mother always has her reasons.
You were born to find Lilia.
I was born to kill you.
We live to serve Mother.
We must obey Mother's
Family Program.
Now it's your turn to die.