Intruder alert!
Silence!
Welcome home, Rion.
I see you have found
Pascalle's daughter.
Good work.
That virus program hidden in her mind...
was the only thing that
ever threatened me.
Now that we have her, nothing can stop me.
I command you to kill her now.
Why do you hesitate?
Do you really think you
can make me kill Lilia?
What's this?
How dare you defy me?!
It's not defiance, just the truth.
I can't!
Rion...
do not be deceived by your memory.
It is not your own.
I loaded it to your brain
from the real Rion.
You are a Galerian.
I made you.
I am your God.
I don't know what to believe...
Listen to your Mother.
Even if I'm not the real Rion...
Even if you did create me...
I'm...
I'm not your slave!
Let's get this over with.
What are you going to do?
Lilia... ready?
Don't!
There's no need to do this!
Ready!
You are my greatest failure.
I never should have created you.
I never should have raised you!
I command you to die.
Death shall be your only salvation.
Dorothy, please stop!